Register of the Papers of Judge John Paul 1930-1964
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- CONDEMNATION CASES
  - H.H. Harmon Land (Augusta) 1942-44 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - B.L. Haymaker Land (Montgomery) 1941-43 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - T.B. Helms Land (Craig) 1941 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - James P. Hewitt Land (Craig) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Elmer V. Hodges Land (Frederick) 1933-37 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Hope and Boguess Land (Botetourt) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - W.S. Hundley Land (Halifax) 1951-52 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - R.S. Hurt Land (Montegomery) 1941-42 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - David Ingram Land (Rockbridge) 1940-41 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Ivanhoe Mining and Smelting Corp. Land 1950-53 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- H-I 1937-51 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Jenkins Land (Rappahannock) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Johannas Jenkins Land (Rappahannock) 1937-39 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Laura Johnston Land (Giles) 1950-57 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - A. Ray Johnston Land (Giles) 1944-45 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - C.C. Jones Land (Craig) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - James Ellwood Jones Estate (Grayson, Smyth and Wythe) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Edwin Jordan Estate (Craig and Alleghany) 1939-41 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Frederick Juchhoff Land (Cumberland) 1938-39 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - Kanawha-Dunlap Land Co. (Alleghany) 1937-59 (Box-folder Box 83)
  - A.C. Keebler Land (Smyth) 1937 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Keystone Coal Co. Land 1933-38 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - James C. Kitzmiller Land (Washington) 1950 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Fayette S. Krenning Land (Wythe) 1941-44 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - A.E. Krise Land (?) 1933-34 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- K 1942-55 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - R.T. Lambeth Land (Augusta) 1939-40 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Schuyler Larkin Land (Craig) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Lorenzo Lawson Land (Montegomery) 1941-44 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - G.W. Layman Land (Craig) 1940-41 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Nancy E. Lee Land (Patrick) 1937-40 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Leftwich Timber Co. (Amherst and Nelson) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Lincoln Investment Co. Land (Grayson and Smyth) 1934-35 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Liquidating Committee of First National Bank of Highland Co. (Bath and Highland) 1935-37 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - W.M. Long Land (Page and Rockingham) 1935-51 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Look and Lincoln, Ltd. Land (Grayson and Smyth) 1935-38 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - J.S. Lowman Land (Page and Rockingham) 1935-40 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- L 1932-51 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Mary S. Malone Land (Montgomery) 1942-51 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Maryland-West Virginia Lumber Co. Land (Shenandoah) 1934 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Hilda Masters Land (Giles) 1948-50 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Thomas B. McCaleb Land (Alleghany) 1939 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Lee McConnell Land (Alleghany) 1941-42 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - A.H. McDannald Land (Alleghany and Bath) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 84)
  - Clyde E. McDannald Land (Alleghany and Bath) 1950-51 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - W.H. McLeod Land (Pulaski) 1941-50 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - L.L. Meador Land (Cumberland) 1939 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - S.R. Millar Estate (Frederick, Shenandoah and Warren) 1935-59 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - A.R. Miller Land (Rockingham) 1936-37 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - F.K. Miller Land (Augusta) 1935-48 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - Octavia V. Miller Land (Rockingham) 1951-52 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - Mineral Development Co. Land (Scott) 1939-40 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - W.C. Moran Land (Bath and Rockbridge) 1936-41 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - Charles W. Morehead Land (Pulaski) 1941-44 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - Ray C. Moyston Land (Halifax) 1950-51 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - James W. Nethers Land (Rappahannock) 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - North Fork Lumber Co. Land (Highland) 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - Sarah O'Riorden Land (Botetourt and Rockbridge) 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - T.A. Parker Land (Alleghany) 1940-51 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - William F. Phillips Land (Rockingham and Shenandoah) 1935-42 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - William S. Pool Land (Halifax) 1952-57 (Box-folder Box 85)
  - Potts Valley Mining & Manufacturing Co. (Alleghany and Craig) 1937-39 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - J.B. Powers & M.E. Tracy Land (Alleghany and Botetourt) 1938 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Clark S. Price Land (Washington) 1949-51 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - M.A. Price Land (Shenandoah) 1939 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Lula M. Pritchard Land (Rockbridge) 1933-36 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Gardner C. Pruett Land (Wythe) 1949 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Pulacki Iron Co. Land (Wythe) 1936-40 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- M-P 1935-59 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Quincy Coal Co. Land (West Virginia) 1934-35 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - H.A. and C.H. Revercomb (Bath) 1940 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Stella Dalton Richardson Land (Montgomery and Pulaski) 1941-49 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - John Riggleman Land (Rockingham) 1935-38 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Roaring Run Land Corp. (Botetourt) 1940-41 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - Anna D. Rock Land (Craig) 1949-58 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - W.V. Rogers Land (Alleghany) 1936-40 (Box-folder Box 86)
  - John E. Roller Estate (Rockingham) 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- R 1934-50 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - Shanklin Farms, Inc. (Smyth) 1936-41 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - William M. Shoun Land 1954 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - H.W. Silsby Land (Arlington) 1958 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - Southwest Virginia Mineral Land Corp. (Lee) 1941-42 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - W.H. Spiller Heirs Land (Smyth) 1939-40 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - J.L. Stanley Land (Grayson) 1933-34 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - J.P. Stevens & Co. (Charlotte and Halifax) (2 folders) 1954-58 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - R.W. Stoneburner Land (Shenandoah) 1937-42 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - T.B. Stuart Land (Charlotte, Halifax and Mecklenburg) 1952-59 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- S 1933-51 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority v. Southern States Power Co. 1939-44 (Box-folder Box 87)
  - H.H. Thomas Land (Alleghany) 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - J. McDaniel Thomas Land (Washington?) 1950-51 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - William R. Thomas Estate (Bath and Highland) 1935-38 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - Tide Water Oil Co. (Bath) 1939-41 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - F.M. Tompkins Land (Lee and Scott) 1936-39 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - L.B. Trigg Land (Montgomery and Pulaski) 1941-46 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - Triton Chemical Land (Botetourt) and Noland Co. v. Triton Chemical [Bankrupt] 1942-43 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- T 1935-59 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - U.S. v. 170.32 Acres of Land n.d. (Box-folder Box 88)
  - United States Lumber Co. (Bath and Highland) 1936-38 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - Virginia Land Bureau (Amherst, Nelson and Rockbridge) 1936 (Box-folder Box 88)
  - W.T. Whitten Land (Amherst and Nelson) 1936-39 (Box-folder Box 89)
  - Olive Vaughan Williams Land (Halifax) 1953-58 (Box-folder Box 89)
  - Lina B. Wittig Land (Rockingham) 1940-42 (Box-folder Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Records & Correspondence -- V-W 1933-49 (Box-folder Box 89)
  - Robert Young Land 1937 (Box-folder Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous Cases: Correspondence, Motions, Pleadings & Orders 1932-36 (Box-folder Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous Cases, Matters Under Two or More Names: Records & Correspondence 1937-38 (Box-folder Box 89)
  - Unknown Cases n.d. (Box-folder Box 89)
- PROFESSIONAL CORRESPONDENCE
  - ABA (American Bar Association) Meeting 1952 (Box-folder Box 90)
  - Alcohol Tax Unit 1939;1943 (Box-folder Box 90)
  - Judge J.L. Almond 1938 (Box-folder Box 90)
  - Judge A.D. Barksdale (7 folders) 1939-64 (Box-folder Box 90)
  - Civil Service Retirement Act 1940-50 (Box-folder Box 90)
  - Criminal Code: Destruction of Mail Boxes 1949 (Box-folder Box 90)
  - Diversity of Citizenship 1949 (Box-folder Box 90)
  - Judge Armistead M. Dobie 1939-42 (Box-folder Box 90)
  - Clarence Gentry: Memorial Service 1963 (Box-folder Box 91)
  - Judicial Conferences (4 folders) 1942-63 (Box-folder Box 91)
  - Juries and Their Role 1940 (Box-folder Box 91)
  - Juvenile Act: Juvenile Delinquency 1941 (Box-folder Box 91)
  - Maintenance of Federal Prisoners in State & County Institutions: Report 1939;1941 (Box-folder Box 91)
  - Military Matters: Desertion 1943 (Box-folder Box 91)
  - Miscellaneous (6 folders) 1930-64 (Box-folder Box 91-92)
  - Naturalization 1940-62 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Judge Paul's Death: Correspondence (J.L. Branch) 1964 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Pre-Trial Conferences 1949 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Pre-Trial Procedure; U.S. Commissioners 1948-55 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Probation Violators 1941-42 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Proposed Legislation: Civil Procedure Rules (2 folders) 1947-48; 1954-55 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Proposed Legislation: Federal Corrections Act (2 folders) 1944-45 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Proposed Legislation: Federal Criminal Laws -- Revision 1943-44 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Proposed Legislation: Federal Judicial Code -- Revision; Rules of Civil Procedure -- Amendments 1939-45 (Box-folder Box 92)
  - Proposed Legislation: Habeas Corpus 1947 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Immigration (McCarran-Walter Act) 1953 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Indeterminate Sentence Bill 1941 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Insane Criminals -- Treatment 1941-42;1946 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Interlocutory Appeals 1952 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Judgeship Bill (Appointment of Additional District Judges) 1952-54 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Miscellaneous 1957-58 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Picketing of Courts; Juvenile Offenders 1948-49 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Richard H. Poff 1955 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Pre-Sentence Reports 1944 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Probationers' Transfer of Jurisdiction 1945-46 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Salary Increase for Judges 1945-46; 1948-49 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Senior Judges' Administrative Duties 1957 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Sentence Reviews by Courts of Appeals in Criminal Cases 1956-57 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Sentencing -- Federal Procedure 1957-58 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Proposed Legislation: Venue Change 1959;1963 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Retirement 1958 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Judge Floyd Roberts 1938-39 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - A. Willis Robertson 1938 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Selective Service Act (5 folders) 1936-1945 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Suffrage Commission; Poll Tax 1945-49 (Box-folder Box 93)
  - Judge Roby Thompson 1957-60 (Box-folder Box 93)
- SPEECHES AND ARTICLES
  - Admission of Attorneys Before the Bar 1937(?) (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Admission to Practice of Resident Attorneys n.d. (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Bankruptcy Act 1934 (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Closing of Big Stone Gap Division 1949 (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Conduct of Judges n.d. (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Conscientious Objectors 1946(?) (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Federal Corrections Act 1942(?) (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Instructions for Commissioner of Shenandoah National Park n.d. (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Qualifications of Attorneys to Practice n.d. (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Rigid Interpretations of Constitution, Wagner Act, Social Security Act, etc. n.d. (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Selection Process of Jurors 1948(?) (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Trends in Federal-State Relations and their Constitutional Implications 1938 (Box-folder Box 94)
  - Voting Rights 1941-45(?) (Box-folder Box 94)